Toni Morrison Papers, 1957-: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1929 September-2015; 100 boxes (3 partial)
  - Subseries 1: Novels, 1929 September-2015; 66 boxes (4 partial)
    - Jazz, 1929 September-1992; 10 boxes (2 partial)
      - Violet/2 revised, 1989 July 13; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - "Putting her hand to something...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Jazz/draft, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - "If I remember right...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
        Page 26.
      - Chapter 10, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
        Page 11.
      - Chapter 7, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 7, 1990 October; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - "She went on like that...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 5, 1991 February 24; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
        Pages 1-34.
      - Chapter 8, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
        Pages 228-235.
      - "...demon in the house.", 1990 July 5; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
        Pages 32-62.
      - Chapter 5, 1991 January 21; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 9, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Jazz End, 1990 December 30; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - "...fingernails tipped with blood.", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
        Pages 3-4.
      - "Daylight slants like a razor...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
        Pages 26-42.
      - "If I remember right...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - "Everybody needs a pile of newspapers...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
        Page 92.
      - "...mother's distraction.", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
        Pages 15-19.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 24, Folder 7)
        Pages 1-284.
      - Draft, 1990 October 16; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Draft, 1990; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
        Pages 31-285.
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 1, Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
      - Draft, 1992; 2 folders (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
      - Setting Copy, 1991; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
      - Sample Pages, 1991 October 22; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - First Pass Proofs Master Set, 1991 November 18; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
      - First Pass Proofs, 1991 November 18; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
      - Second Pass Proofs Master Set, 1991 December 19; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 8, Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Second Pass Proofs, 1991 December 19; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
      - Third Pass Proofs, 1992 February 4-17; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
      - Cut Proofs, 1992 February 4; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
      - Knopf Canada Proof Pages, 1992 February-March; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - F&Gs, 1992 March 19; 1 item (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Blueline Proofs, 1992; 1 item (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Advance Copy, 1992; 1 item (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Production Mock-up, 1992; 1 item (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Paradise, 1994-2014; 13 boxes (1 partial)
      - Research Material, 1995-2013; 2 boxes
        - Brazil, undated; 3 folders (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
        - Gibson, Arrell Morgan: Oklahoma: A History of Five Centuries, undated; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - Historical Atlas of Oklahoma, undated; 1 item (Box 30, Folder 5)
          Photocopied book, published by the University of Oklahoma Press, 1986.
        - Miscellaneous, undated; 2 folders (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
          Includes letter from Lois Brooks.
        - Nicodemus, undated; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - Oklahoma, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - The Oklahoma Story, undated; 1 item (Box 31, Folder 3)
          Photocopied book, published by the University of Oklahoma Press, 1978.
        - Photographs, 1996; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - Schwendemann, Glen: Nicodemus: Negro Haven on the Solomon, undated; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 5)
          Photocopied document, published by the State of Kansas Commission on Civil Rights, June 1971.
        - Soil Survey Series, 1995; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Research for 2014 Introduction, 2013; 2 folders (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
      - Outlines and Notes, circa 1994-1997; 2 folders (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
      - "Fleetwood", undated; 1 folder Notepad pages. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - "They shoot the white girl first...", undated; 1 folder Notepad pages. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - "3rd Chapel", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - "He looked back...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - "Green persimmon", undated; 1 folder Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - "1963/Soane's abortion...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - "In the deepest part of the cellar...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - "1. Soane and Dovey...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - "Some must see in order to believe...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - "Feelings/Friendship w/ Soane..", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - "1. 'Pity' for what she sees in Pallas' womb...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - "1. Accident in front of Convent...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - "Color Coded instances", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - "O Holy Night", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - "No doubt about it...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 2)
        Includes notes for "On the Backs of Blacks."
      - "Sweetie wouldn't discuss it...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - "She had no (driver's) license...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - "K.D. wears the dashiki and Pro-Keds", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - "Grace 1970", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - "via K.D.", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - "Brow", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - "Chap. 4 Cont'd", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - "She said 'Where will you bury them?'", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - "Too early for cellar", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - "To New Mexico with Guy...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - "When chasing dreams...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - "Patricia/Did not try...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - War, undated; 1 folder Printouts. (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - The Bake Oven, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Early Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Early Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout. (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Early Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Early Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Early Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 17)
        Chapters One and Two; pages 1-23, 12-13.
      - Ruby, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Ruby, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Ruby, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 33, Folder 20)
        Pages 2-18.
      - Ruby, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Ruby, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Ruby, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Ruby, 1994 August 12; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Ruby, 1994 August 15; 1 folder Printout. (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Ruby, 1994 August 15; 1 folder Printout. (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Ruby, 1994 August 24; 1 folder Printout. (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Ruby, 1994 December 8; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 2)
        Pages 2-24.
      - Mavis Notes, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Mavis, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Mavis, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 34, Folder 5)
        Pages 4-8.
      - Mavis, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Mavis, 1994 July 29; 1 folder Printout. (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Mavis, 1994 July 29; 1 folder Printout. (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Mavis, 1994 August 15; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Mavis, 1994 August 16; 1 folder Printout. (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Mavis, 1994 August 26; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Mavis, 1994 August 26; 1 folder Printout. (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Mavis, 1994 August 26; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Mavis, 1994 December 8; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Chapter 2: Mavis, July 5; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 15)
        Pages 27-78.
      - Grace, 1994 August 18; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Grace, 1994 August 26; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 17)
        Pages 1-25; 31-33.
      - Grace, 1994 August 26; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Grace, 1994 August 26; 1 folder Printout, corrected (photocopy). (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Chapter 3: Grace, July 2; 1 folder Printout, corrected; photocopy. (Box 34, Folder 20)
        Pages 79-122; photocopy of pages 97-101.
      - Seneca, 1994 September 10; 1 folder Printout. (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Seneca, 1994 September 15; 1 folder Printout, corrected and photocopy. (Box 34, Folder 22)
        Pages 1-16; photocopy of pages 2-16..
      - Seneca, 1994 September 10; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Seneca, 1994 December 19; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 24)
        Pages 4-29.
      - Seneca, 1995 May 20; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 25)
        Pages 94-132.
      - Seneca, 1995 June 2; 1 folder Printout. (Box 34, Folder 26)
        Pages 94-136.
      - Chapter 4: Seneca, June 30; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 27)
        Pages 123-218 (red pencil 222).
      - Chapter 4: Seneca, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 34, Folder 28)
        Pages 123-207.
      - Chapter 5: Divine, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 1)
        Pages 203-214.
      - Chapter 5: Divine, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 2)
        Pages 205-229.
      - Chapter 5: Divine, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 3)
        Pages 205-267.
      - Chapter 5: Divine, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 4)
        Pages 205-238.
      - Chapter 5: Divine, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 35, Folder 5)
        Pages 208-213.
      - Chapter 5: Divine, July 2; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 6)
        Pages 208-279 (pencil 219-290; red pencil 223).
      - Patricia, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 7)
        Pages 280-297.
      - Patricia, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 8)
        Pages 280-298.
      - Patricia, September 8; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 9)
        Pages 280-294; with "Pat's notes," numbered pp.13-16.
      - Patricia, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 35, Folder 10)
        Pages 280-299.
      - Patricia, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 11)
        Pages 281-307.
      - Chapter 6: Patricia, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 12)
        Pages 280-310 (pencil 291-321).
      - Chapter 6: Patricia, June 11; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 13)
        Pages 291-334.
      - Chapter 6: Patricia, July 1; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 14)
        Pages 291-346.
      - Chapter 6: Patricia, July 1; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 15)
        Pages 291-348 (pen 297-354).
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 18)
        Pages 322-328.
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 19)
        Pages 322-338.
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 35, Folder 20)
        Pages 322-354.
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, April 29; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 21)
        Pages 322-357.
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, June 20; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 22)
        Pages 322 (pen 347)-359.
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, June 25; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 23)
        Pages 347-397.
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, July 11; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 24)
        Pages 347 (pencil 349)-401.
      - Chapter 7: Consolata, August 11; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 35, Folder 25)
        Pages 349 (pencil 354, 355)-433.
      - Lone, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 8: Lone, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 8: Lone, July 30; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 8: Lone, August 3; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 4)
        Pages 434-454.
      - Chapter 8: Lone, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 5)
        Pages 434-457.
      - Chapter 8: Lone, August 8; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 6)
        Pages 436-462.
      - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 21; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 21; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 8)
        Pages 480-487.
      - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 23; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 23, Folder 9)
        Pages 480-496.
      - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 26; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 10)
        Pages 480-498.
      - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 28; 1 folder Printout. (Box 36, Folder 11)
        Pages 480-512.
      - Draft Fragments, circa 1994-1997; 2 folders Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
      - Draft, 1995 January 3; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Draft, 1995 April 23; 1 item Printout. (Box 36, Folder 15)
        Pages 1-124.
      - Draft, 1995 June 12; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 36, Folder 16)
        Pages 1-165.
      - Draft, 1995 August 10; 1 item Printout. (Box 36, Folder 17)
        Pages 1-171.
      - Draft, 1996 June 10; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 37, Folder 1)
        Pages 1-202.
      - Draft, circa 1996-1997; 1 item Printout (photocopy). (Box 37, Folder 2)
        Pages 1-203.
      - Draft, 1997 July 12; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 37, Folder 3-6)
        Pages 1-517.
      - Draft, circa 1997; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Folder 38, Folder 1-3)
        Pages 1-534.
      - Setting Copy, 1997; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 38, Folder 4-6)
      - First Pass Rough Pages Duplicate, 1997 October 20; 1 item (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
      - First Pass Master Set, 1997 October 21; 1 item (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
      - Second Pass Proofs Author Set, 1997 November 3; 1 item (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
      - Second Pass Proofs Master Set, 1997 November 3; 1 item (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Third Pass Proofs, 1997 November 11; 1 item (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
      - Blueline Proofs with Corrected Pages, 1997; 1 item (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Advance Copy, 1998; 1 item (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Foreword, 2005; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Introduction, circa 2014; 1 folder Notepad pages, corrected printout and photocopy. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Love, 2000-2003; 7 boxes
      Working titles Sporting Woman and L.
      - Outlines and Notes, 2000-2003; 2 folders (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
      - "The settlement is a planet away from Cosey's Resort...", undated; 1 folder Notepad pages. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - "Do you like my Boyfriend?", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - "helpmate. Content to serve.", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - "L.3. The Ocean is my man now.", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - "Chapter Six (Bachelor)", undated; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - "Chap. 3 The sad little orange trees...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - "She didn't need to know...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - "Notes: material tk", undated; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - "The boots, probably, which she never took off...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - "Families make the best enemies...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - "So he planned an outing with Romen.", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - "afraid L's threat...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - "The bottled cotton-mouth...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - "Burrowing under blankets...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - "i.e. so hot...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - "Sketch for Chap. Nine 'Father'", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - "Jailhouse", undated; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - "Last chap.", undated; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - "A Sporting Woman", undated; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - "MS" [Early Drafts], 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Chapter 1, 2000 December 2-2001 April 19; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 1)
        Pages 14-43.
      - Chapter 2, 2001 January 5-April 26; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - 2001 January 5, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - 2001 April 26, 1 item
      - L: B, 2000 July 28-2001 April 19; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - 2000 July 28, 1 item
        - 2001 January 1, 1 item
        - 2000 December 14, 1 item
        - 2000 December 2, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - 2001 February 15, 1 item
        - 2001 April 19, 1 item
      - Chapter 4, undated; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 5, 2001 July 23; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 12, undated; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Chapter Drafts, 2000 July 28-2001 May 10; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 1, 2001 April 19-April 26; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
          Pages 1-45.
        - Chapter 3, 2001 May 10; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 1, 2000 August 3; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
          Page 12.
        - Sporting Woman, 2000 July 28; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
          Pages 10-35.
      - Sporting Woman, 2000 July 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Sporting Woman, 2000 July 10; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 2, 2001 January 2; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
        1 p.
      - "That flooded his chest", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 2, 2001 January 2; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Sporting Woman, 2000 July 28; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 2, 2000 December 29; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 4, 2001 January 2; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - "Filed as Junior Vivian", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 3, 2001 May 10; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 3, 2001 May 10; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - L, 2001 July 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 10, 2001 July 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 1, 2002 May 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - L2, 2002 August 14; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - L2, 2002 August 14; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 7: Guardian, 2002 August 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 8: Father, 2002 September 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - L5, 2002 September 26; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 8: Father, 2002 November 11; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 November 11; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - L4, 2002 November 13; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 7, 2002 December 2; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 5: Lover, 2002 July 9; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 6: Husband, 2002 July 8; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - SW Chapter 1 (including L1), December 16; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - L4, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - L2, December 22; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - "Sometimes children fall in love...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - L5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - L4, 2002 June 3; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - L4, 2002 September 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - L, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - L, 2002 September 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
        Pages 8-9.
      - Chapter 7, 2002 August 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 4: Benefactor, 2002 June 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - End of Chapter 4, 2002 June 3; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 August 26; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 August 13; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 August 13; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 8 [Originally SW Chap 9], 2002 August 26; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 1, 2002 October 1; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 6 [Original Chap. 7/Husband], 2002 November 13; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 7, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 7: Guardian, 2002 August 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 5: Lover, 2002 June 3; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - L, 2002 June 27; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - L2, 2002 June 27; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 5, 2002 June 27; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 6 [Original Chap. 7/Husband], 2002 July 2; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 1: Image, 2002 July 3; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
        Pages 15-45.
      - Chapter 6 [Original Chap. 7/Husband], 2002 July 8; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 5: Lover, 2002 July 9; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - L3, 2002 August 12; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - L3, 2002 August 12; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Corrections pp. 1-8 reprinted, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - L5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)